A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 45267], 1969-2008 [bulk 1995-2004]., Extent: 15 cu. ft. (15 boxes). (Box 1-15)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Danville Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Germanna Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - New River Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Piedmont Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Danville Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Germanna Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - New River Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Piedmont Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Danville Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Germanna Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - New River Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Piedmont Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Danville Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Germanna Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - New River Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Piedmont Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Danville Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Germanna Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - New River Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Piedmont Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Constitution, by-laws, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Danville Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Germanna Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - John Tyler Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - New River Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Tidewater Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Wytheville Community College, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Danville Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Germanna Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - John Tyler Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - New River Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Tidewater Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Wytheville Community College, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Danville Community College, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Germanna Community College, 1994 (Box 9)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1994 (Box 9)
  - John Tyler Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - New River Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Tidewater Community College, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Virginia Higlands Community College, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Peninsula Workforce Development Center, Thomas Nelson Community College, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Mgt. of Amewrican, inc., 2004 (Box 11)
  - Restructuring, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Restructuring, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Restructuring, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Restructuring, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Restructuring, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Early retirement information, 2006 (Box 11)
  - VCCS - 29 (Box 11)
  - VCCS - 29, 2003 (Box 11)
  - VCCS - 29, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Faculty salary plan approvals, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Survey results (Box 11)
  - State Board meeting, 2004 (Box 11)
  - State Board meeting, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Dual enrollment, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Commonwealth classrooms, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Strategic planning, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Issues assessment report, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Workforce Development Taskforce, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Freedom of Information requests, 2006 (Box 11)
  - Task force on Dateline, 2009 (Box 11)
  - Dateline, 2009 (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Administration, 2005 (Box 11)
  - Attorney General, 2006 (Box 11)
  - JLARC, 2003 (Box 11)
  - JLARC, 2002 (Box 11)
  - JLARC, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Joint subcommittee on Higher Education, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Joint subcommittee on Higher Education, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Joint subcommittee on Higher Education, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Budget reduction plans, 2002-2003 (Box 11)
  - Budget, Final, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 11)
  - Tuition increases, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education Restructuring Act, 2007 (Box 11)
  - Campus Master Planning, 1992 (Box 11)
  - JLARC recommendations and VCCS responses, 1987-1992 (Box 12)
  - Distance learning proposals, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Task force on Attracting, Selecting and Retaining Faculty, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Institutional research Steering Committee, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Lab hours Task Force, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Student Information System Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Task force on attracting and retaining faculty, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Task force on cross referencing of courses in the VCCS, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Task force on intercollegiate athletes, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Textbook task force, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Task force on variability of credit hours (Box 12)
  - Information infrastructure task force, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Information infrastructure task force, 1994 (Box 12)
  - VCCS - 29 Task force (Box 12)
  - Task force formation (Box 12)
  - Distance education (Box 12)
  - Administrative salaries Ad Hoc Committee. 1994 (Box 12)
  - Computer Ethics and Computer Security Work groups, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Budget Advocacy Steering Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
  - Distance learning compenstaion committee, 1995 (Box 12)
  - State Board for Community Colleges, Briefing, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Off Campus Lease Audit, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Tech Prep in Virginia Facts and Figures, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Principles of Good Practice for Dual-Credit Programs, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Enhancing Support for Adjunct Faculty, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Training and Business Assistance Services, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Classified Staff Professional Development Committee Report, 1994 (Box 13)
  - A World Class Workforce: Virginia's Strategy for Economic Development, 1998 (Box 13)
  - The Role of Technology in Support of Developmental Education, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Report of the Committee on Dual Enrollment Fees (HJR 562), 1997 (Box 13)
  - Creating and Sustaining an Information Technology Future in the VCCS, 1994 (Box 13)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia Degree Programs by Institution, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Enrollment Projections Virginia's State-Supported Institutions of Higher Education, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Study of Preparing A Skilled Workforce for the 21st Century, House Document No. 18, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Final Report HJR No. 143, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Annual Report of the Virginia Business Education Partnership Program, 1994 (Box 13)
  - The Next Steps, Development of a Fully Productive Workforce in Virginia in the 1990's (Box 13)
  - Annual Report of the Workforce Virginia 2000 Advocacy Council, 1994 (Box 13)
  - The Establishment and Vision of the Workforce Leadership Council, 1994 (Box 13)
  - VCCS 2002 General Obligation Bond Project Descriptions (Box 13)
  - The Virginia Plan for Strenghtening the Commonwealth's 21st Century Workforce, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Developing Virginia's Commitment to Global Competitiveness, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Recommendations of the Governor's Blue Ribbon Commission on Higher Education, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Non-Credit Funding, HRJ 622, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Community College System Responses on the Impact of Budget Reductions, 1993 (Box 13)
  - A Report on the Practices of Colleges in the VCCS and their relationship with Old Dominion University and Teletechnet, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Educational Programs and Services Handbook, 1992 (Box 13)
  - VCCS Utiliation of Classrooms and Labs, 1998 (Box 13)
  - The Commonwealth's Link to a 21st Century Quality Workforce, House Document No. 10, 1993 (Box 13)
  - JLARC Report to the General Assembly of Virginia, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Tuition and Fee Rates for 2004-2005 (Box 13)
  - Capital Outlay Request for 2000-02 and Six-Year Capital Outlay Plan (Box 13)
  - Impact Report on Relocation of Portsmouth Campus Tidewater Community College, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Report of the Committee on Dual Enrollment Fees, HRJ 562, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Dateline 2009 Progress Report for Workforce Development, 2007 (Box 13)
  - Report of the Task Force on Continuing Education and Non-Credit Instruction (Box 13)
  - Building a Better Virginia Foundation, 2002 (Box 13)
  - VCCS Quater to Semester Conversion, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Community College System 260, 1999 session, Amendments, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Valid Resource Distribution, 2007-2008 (Box 13)
  - Overhead presentations (Box 13)
  - Policy manual changes, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 1999-2000 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Policy manual changes, 2007 (Box 14)
  - VCCS, Policies, Procedures and Regulations, Operating Manual, Volume I, 1969 (Box 15)
  - VCCS, Policies, Procedures and Regulations, Operating Manual, Volume II, 1969 (Box 15)
  - VCCS, Policies, Procedures and Regulations, Operating Manual, 1972-1977 (Box 15)
  - A Proposed Master Plan for a State-Wide System of Community College Education in Virginia, ca. 1970 (Box 15)
  - Enrollments in the Virginia Community College System, Instructional Leadership Seminar, 1995 (Box 15)
- Series VII: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 50877], 1988-2005., Extent: 15 cu. ft. (15 boxes). (Box 1-15)
  - Assessment Status Reports, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Dual Enrollment Task Force, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Virginia Plan for Dual Enrollment between VA Public Schools and Community Colleges, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Assessment in Majors, SCHEV, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Assessment Status Reports, 1988 (Box 1)
  - VCCS Assessment Task Force Reporting, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Dual Enrollment, 1989-1991 (Box 1)
  - Assessment Guidelines, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Dual Enrollment of High School Students, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Interim Assessment Reports, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Progress Report Letters, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Report of the General Education Task Force, 1990, Part 1 of 2 (Box 1)
  - Report of the General Education Task Force, 1990, Part 2 of 2 (Box 1)
  - Student Assessment Progress Reports, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper article, Dual Enrollment Encourages Head start, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Dual Credit Enrollments, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Dual Enrollment, A Policy Related Question, 1991 (Box 1)
  - VCCS Enrollment Report, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Dual Credit, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Program Review Methods, VCCS Community Colleges, 1993 (Box 1)
  - SACS Report of the Reaffirmation Committee JTCC, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Categories of Dual Enroll Students, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Dual Enrollment and Advanced Placement, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Focus Group Report Articulation, Transfer, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper article, Dual Enrollment, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Proposed Degree Program, DCC, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Report of the Reaffirmation Committee, Dabney S. Lancaster CC, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Special Reports - GCC, JTCC, TNSS, VHCC, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Institutional Self Study Report, 1993-1995 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, SACS Accreditation report, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
  - Assessment Cover Letters from Colleges, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Assessment Reporting Guidelines, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Assessment Reporting, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Assessment Teleconference, 1995 (Box 2)
  - College Evaluations, Commendations, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Dual Enrolled Students, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Interim Assessment, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Oral Assessment Reports, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Assessment Guidelines, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Assessment Progress, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Assessment Summaries, Letters, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Dual Credit Materials, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Dual Enrollment, Dual Credit Handbooks from Colleges, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Request for Recognition of General Studies Degree, 1996 (Box 3)
  - SACS Accreditation Second Follow Up Report, Central Virginia CC, 1996 (Box 3)
  - State Committee on Transfer of General Studies, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Evaluation Summaries, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Letters, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reporting Guidelines, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster CC General Studies, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Dual Credit, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Dual Credit, MOU, 1997 (Box 3)
  - General Studies Request, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Principles of Good Practice for Dual Credit Programs, 1997 (Box 3)
  - SCHEV Assessment Guidelines, 1998 (Box 3)
  - General Education Survey, 1998 (Box 3)
  - General Studies, 1996-1998 (Box 3)
  - Report on General Education in Virginia, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Report, Germanna CC, 1999 (Box 3)
  - General Studies, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Blue Ridge CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Central Virginia CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Dabney S. Lancaster CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Danville CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Eastern Shore CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Germanna CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, John Tyler CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Lord Fairfax CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Mountain Empire CC, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Assessment Reports, Northern Virginia CC, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Assessment Reports, Patrick Henry CC, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Assessment Reports, Paul D. Camp CC, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Assessment Reports, Piedmont Virginia CC, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Assessment Reports, Southside Virginia CC, 2001 (Box 4)
  - English 111 Writing Sample, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Summary of Comments from Regional Meetings for Assessing Writing and Technology Competencies, 2001 (Box 4)
  - VCCS Transfer Among Colleges, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Writing Competencies, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Business Management Degree Program, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Amended SCHEV Guidelines, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Programs, National Recognition, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Program Productivity, SCHEV, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Program Review, College Reports, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Program Review, Productivity VCCS, 2002 (Box 4)
  - VCCS Holistic Scoring Workshop, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Program Revitalization, 2003 (Box 4)
  - General Studies, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Government Offices, Misc., 2001 (Box 4)
  - Higher Education in Virginia, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Hope Scholarship, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Human Resources Services, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Information Technology, Vice Chancellor, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Inauguration of Dr. Ann Alexander, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Instructional Technology, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Jobs for America's Graduates, Inc., 2001 (Box 4)
  - Jobs for the Future, 2001 (Box 4)
  - National Council of State Directors of Community Colleges, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Performance Communications Group, Academic Affairs and Government Relations, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Public Affairs, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Senate, State of Virginia, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Southern Association of colleges and Schools, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Plan, VCCS, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Student Information System Information, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Treasury, Dept. of, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Ukrops, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Business Higher Education Council, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Campus Compact, 2001 (Box 4)
  - VCCS Annual meeting, 2001 (Box 4)
  - VCCS Distance Learning Initiative and V2U, 2001 (Box 4)
  - VCCS Enrollment, 1995-2001 (Box 4)
  - VCCS, Utility, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia College Savings Plan, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Retirement System, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Space Grant Consortium, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Workforce Training Council, 2001 (Box 4)
  - House of Delegates, 2002 (Box 5)
  - HJR 159, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Immigration Law, 2002 (Box 5)
  - International Education, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Information Technology, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Internal Audit, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 5)
  - JLARC Study, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Joint Conference Committee Report, 2002 (Box 5)
  - JLARC, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Services, Division of, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Library of Virginia, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Local College Board Members, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Middle College, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Old Dominion University, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Profiles in Leadership, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Project Lead the Way, 2002 (Box 5)
  - SB 681, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Public Affairs, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Senate of Virginia, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Southern Association of Community Colleges, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Treasury, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Technology, Secretary of, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Transportation, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 5)
  - University of Virginia, 2002 (Box 5)
  - U.S. Dept. of Education, 2002 (Box 5)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Business Higher Education Council, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Campus Compact, 2002 (Box 5)
  - VCCS Compact and Student Tuition increase, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Retirement System, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virtual Library of Virginia, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Workforce Council, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Business Assistance, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Tech, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Workforce Development Services, 2002 (Box 5)
  - 2001 May (Box 5)
  - 2001 July (Box 5)
  - 2001 August (Box 5)
  - 2001 September (Box 5)
  - 2001 October (Box 5)
  - 2001 November (Box 5)
  - 2001 December (Box 5)
  - 2003 January (Box 5)
  - 2003 February (Box 5)
  - 2003 March (Box 5)